Finding Aid for Personnel Office (University of Michigan) Records, 1940-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Labor Relations
  - History of Labor Relations at University of Michigan
    - Union Security Clauses and Agency Shops, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - Licensed Practical Nurses, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Library Staff Association, 1968 (Box 30)
  - National Council of Distributive Workers of America (NCDWA), Local 826, 1971; undated (Box 30)
  - Pharmacists' Association, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Printers' Union, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Professional/Administrative Unions, 1971-1974 (Box 30)
  - Resident Advisors, 1971-1972 (Box 30)
  - Security Guards' Union, 1984; 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Student Employees' Association
    - 1964-1965 (Box 30)
    - 1969-1974 (Box 30)
  - Teamsters' Organizing Drive, 1970; 1973 (Box 30)
  - Telephone Counselors (BOOGIE-Benevolent Order of Guides In Extremis), 1972 (Box 30)
- Salary Equity Study, 1987-1989
  - Salary Data, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
  - Final Report, 1989 (Box 34)
- Attitude Surveys, 1969-1980
  - 1965 Survey, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Survey, 1966
    - Final Report, 1966 (Box 34)
    - Questionnaire and Responses, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Survey, 1967
    - Analysis of all Schools and Colleges, 1967; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Analysis of Non-Instructional Units, 1967 (Box 34)
    - Response Range, 1967 (Box 34)
    - Staff Questionnaire Rankings, 1967 (Box 34)
  - Survey, 1972
    - Correspondence, 1972; 1974 (Box 34)
    - Questionnaire Work Sheets, 1972 (Box 34)
  - Survey, 1977
    - Comparisons with 1972 Survey, 1964, 1978-1980 (Box 34)
    - Results, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - 1979 Survey of University Hospital, 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 34)
- Faculty Handbook Files, 1979-1990
  - Appointments, 1989; 1990 (Box 35)
  - Authorized Absences, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - Booklets from Office of Staff Benefits, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Compensation, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Conditions of Use: Computing Facilities, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Contents Through, 8/16/1989; 1989; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Discrepancies Between Standard Practice Guide and Bylaws, 1980; 1986 (Box 36)
  - Discrimination/Harassment, 1986; 1989 (Box 36)
  - Documents Available Through Units, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Drafts, 1989-1990; 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Faculty, 1976-1985 (Box 36)
  - Faculty Notes/Articles, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Freedom of Speech and Artistic Expression, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Edit of 1978 Instructional Staff Handbook, circa 1982 (Box 36)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - General Information Guide
    - Benefits, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
    - Educational Opportunities, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Michigan Information Guide, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Other Services, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Other University Regulations, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Governance, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Grievances, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Integrity of Scholarship, 1986 (Box 36)
  - Non-Discrimination, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Ongoing, 1986-1989 (Box 36)
  - Other Academic Regulations, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Preface, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Promo/Termination/Appeal, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Regulations Governing Teaching and Research, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Regulations Governing Working Conditions, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Relationships with Outside Agencies, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Research, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Research Support Services, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Retirement, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Revisions, 1993; 4 folders (Box 36)
    (1-4 of 7 folders)
  - Revisions, 1993; 3 folders (Box 37)
    (5-7 of 7 folders)
  - Revisions of 1982 Handbook, 1982 (Box 37)
  - Sabbaticals, 1986-1989 (Box 37)
  - Schools and Colleges, 1989 (Box 37)
  - Student Relations, 1989 (Box 37)
  - Support, 1989 (Box 37)
  - Technical Revisions, 1986 (Box 37)
  - Tenure, 1985-1989 (Box 37)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1986 (Box 37)
- Topical Files, 1973-1979
  - 1973-1979
    - Accessibility and Disability Issues
      - Access: "Managing a Barrier Free Environment,", 1990 (Box 38)
      - Accessibility Taskforce
        - Building Needs, 1983-1997 (Box 38)
        - General, 1991-2000; 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Affirmative Action Handicap Report, 1986 (Box 38)
      - Council for Disability Concerns, 1990-1999; 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Education Taskforce (Psychiatric Disabilities), 1985 (Box 38)
      - Employment Taskforce (Accommodation Fund), 1991-1996 (Box 38)
      - Learning Disability Report, 1987 (Box 38)
    - Attendance System, 1973; 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Dependent Care Taskforce, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Symposium
      - 1988 (Box 39)
      - 1989 (Box 39)
    - Retirement
      - Compulsory, 1982-1992; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Taskforce on Faculty Retirement, 1993 (Box 39)
      - Taskforce on Faculty Retirement Report, 1993 (Box 39)
      - Women's Forum, 1988 (Box 39)